

Huma Dawari

Date of birth: 30/07/2002 | **Nationality:** Afghan | **Gender:** Female | **Phone number:**

(+93) 0744496570 (Mobile) | Email address: humadawari@gmail.com | Instagram:

https://instagram.com/humadawari?igshid=MmVIMilkMTBhMg== | **Whatsapp Messenger:** 0744496570

Address: Kandahar Aino Mena, street 11, 3801, Aino Mena, Afghanistan (Home)

ABOUT ME

I graduated from school with 98% first class A, I'm an English graduate, I'm very good at time management and discipline in my personal and work life, I'm very hardworking person and I have good social communication. I was very interested in computer subjects at school. After school, I wanted to start computer science, but in our society, people think that a woman should either become a doctor or a teacher, so I had chosen medicine at Ghalib university-Kabul-Afghanistan to become a professional doctor. But two years ago our university was closed to girls forever, but I am very interested in computers and technology, If I can study in the field of computers, which is my favorite field since childhood, and I am very creative in the field of computers and technology, and in school, my grades were always 100% in computer subjects.

My future vision of me in computer science is that I will make a lot of progress in this field because I love computer science and I will have a lot of creativity.

I am certified and trained in these field through UNDP.

- 1 Fundraising and grant proposal writing.
- 2 Financial management and budgeting.
- 3 Monitoring , Evaluation and learning.
- 4 Advocacy and lobbying techniques.
- 5 Project planning and implementation.
- 6 Gander mainstreaming and inclusivity.
- 7 Human resources management and development.
- 8 Community mobilization and engagement.
- 9 Strategic planning and organizational development.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

06/09/2007 - 28/12/2018 Lashkar gah, Afghanistan

SCHOOL GRADUATE Markazi Girls High School

Address Helmand, Lashkar gah, street 22, 3902, Lashkar gah, Afghanistan

WORK EXPERIENCE

06/11/2019 - 28/12/2022 Helmand, Afghanistan

VOICE PRESIDENT NGO- OBA (ORGANIZATION OF BASIC ADVANCEMENT)

I was the voice president of this NGO that was working freely.

Because I was the voice president, I had almost many qualifications that we had to adjust the plan, consider the scope, under what condition and when we should manage this project, time management and new challenges.

- Making plan in which areas it is necessary to give general awareness to women about hygiene so that they can take care of themselves, their families and their children.
- for women, we arranged free courses in English and since topics in Helmand province.
- In animal husbandry, we gave face to face training to women to learn animal husbandry and again financial independence.
- We gave training to people in TB on how they can take care of their family and themselves.

• We used to send ambulances to different areas to bring people who needed urgent care to the hospital, so I had to check which areas I should send these ambulances to .

Address Helmand Afghanistan, 3904, Helmand, Afghanistan

01/03/2019 - 01/08/2019 Helmand, Afghanistan

SPORTS TEACHER BOST HIGH SCHOOL

I was the sports teacher who taught students workout, football and volleyball.

DIGITAL SKILLS

Social Media | Video Conferencing (Zoom, Teams, Skype, Webex) - Advanced | Microsoft Office package: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access | Editing Photo / Video | Adobe Photoshop (basic elements)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **PASHTO**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
PERSIAN	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2
DARI	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2
URDU	C2	B1	C2	C2	B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Football I like football very much and I have been watching it since childhood.

Study Study is one of my best hobbies that I never get tired of.

Travel We do a lot of family travel.

Volleyball I have been playing volleyball since I was a child.

Music Music can be very relaxing for me.